<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on The KosmosGhost Site</title>
    <link>https://kosmosghost.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on The KosmosGhost Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:53:49 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kosmosghost.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Picture Book of all the Apps on Mobile Linux</title>
      <link>https://kosmosghost.github.io/posts/a-picture-book-of-all-the-apps-on-mobile-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:53:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kosmosghost.github.io/posts/a-picture-book-of-all-the-apps-on-mobile-linux/</guid>
      <description>This is a non-exhaustive list of the Apps I&amp;rsquo;ve been using on my Mobile Linux device.
AI Weather Web Browsing Plasma Tube Audio Books Podcasts Music Video Player EBooks RSS File Sync Password Manager Games Mastodon Matrix Software Store Anti-Spam AI: Bavarder works with many of the AI chat bots. Unfortunately, I am out of storage on my phone, so I haven&amp;rsquo;t been able to try Llama.cpp yet.
Weather: The weather app looks like a professional mobile app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reinstall Android on Oneplus6 or Oneplus6t Device After Installing Mobile Linux</title>
      <link>https://kosmosghost.github.io/posts/reinstall-android-on-oneplus6-or-oneplus6t-device-after-installing-mobile-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 19:50:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kosmosghost.github.io/posts/reinstall-android-on-oneplus6-or-oneplus6t-device-after-installing-mobile-linux/</guid>
      <description>Did you install a Mobile Linux Operating System onto your Oneplus6 or Oneplus6t device, and you want to go back to android? Well, you&amp;rsquo;re in luck as it&amp;rsquo;s a pretty straight forward process.
First, download the package from Oneplus. This can be done by going to service.oneplus.com/us. Scroll down to the image that says Software Update and then click on it. You will now be at a page that has a list of devices with links for firmware for the devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing PostmarketOS With Full Disk Encryption on Oneplus6 Oneplus6t Devices</title>
      <link>https://kosmosghost.github.io/posts/installing-postmarketos-with-full-disk-encryption-on-oneplus6-oneplus6t-devices/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 19:30:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kosmosghost.github.io/posts/installing-postmarketos-with-full-disk-encryption-on-oneplus6-oneplus6t-devices/</guid>
      <description>Installing PostmarketOS on the Oneplus 6/6t devices is pretty easy, and you will have a linux operating system on your phone with full disk encryption. By following this short tutorial you can have a mobile linux operating system on your phone in no time, but this tutorial assumes you are using linux for doing the install. Before you start you are going to need a few tools:
Android tools for fastboot - On Fedora: sudo dnf install android-tools</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
