<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on The KosmosGhost Site</title>
    <link>https://kosmosghost.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on The KosmosGhost Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 01:34:19 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kosmosghost.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Running Firefox in its own container</title>
      <link>https://kosmosghost.github.io/posts/running-firefox-in-a-container.-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 01:34:19 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kosmosghost.github.io/posts/running-firefox-in-a-container.-part-1/</guid>
      <description>A word of warning: Please do not assume that following this tutorial will add anything to your internet security. I created this guide because I couldn&amp;rsquo;t really find anything about running Firefox in its own container.
A quick suggestion: When I was trying to really find out about containers and namespaces, I made a mistake of web searching with a search string that would include the word, &amp;ldquo;container.&amp;rdquo; This turned out to be a painful experience since most web searches would return information on Docker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Qemu Comparison</title>
      <link>https://kosmosghost.github.io/posts/a-qemu-comparison/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 23:42:40 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kosmosghost.github.io/posts/a-qemu-comparison/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to create a build system on my X86-64 laptop that would cross-compile apps, and then package them in the alpine *.apk format. Did I accomplish this task? Yes. Will I be using my build system? Nope.
Why?
qemu-aarch64: real 1h 8m 39s user 4h 21m 47s sys 2m 16.29s x84_64: real 2m 13.35s user 11m 10.88s sys 0m 23.99s That&amp;rsquo;s right. In took over an hour to cross-compile and package the software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So, You Bricked PmOS</title>
      <link>https://kosmosghost.github.io/posts/so-you-bricked-pmos/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 23:15:27 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kosmosghost.github.io/posts/so-you-bricked-pmos/</guid>
      <description>Oh no! You broke the GUI while doing an upgrade with pmOS. It might be possible to fix it with chroot, and this short tutorial will show you how.
The following was tested using an x86 laptop, and a oneplus6t-fajita running postmarketOS.
First things, first. This is a real good opportunity to back up your data. Try to keep that in mind while you are doing this tutorial.
Download jumpdrive Download jumpdrive from here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Picture Book of some of the Apps on Mobile Linux</title>
      <link>https://kosmosghost.github.io/posts/a-picture-book-of-some-of-the-apps-on-mobile-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:53:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kosmosghost.github.io/posts/a-picture-book-of-some-of-the-apps-on-mobile-linux/</guid>
      <description>This is a non-exhaustive list of the Apps I&amp;rsquo;ve been using on my Mobile Linux device.
AI Weather Web Browsing Plasma Tube Audio Books Podcasts Music Video Player EBooks RSS File Sync Password Manager Games Mastodon Matrix Software Store Anti-Spam AI: Bavarder works with many of the AI chat bots. Unfortunately, I am out of storage on my phone, so I haven&amp;rsquo;t been able to try Llama.cpp yet.
Weather: The weather app looks like a professional mobile app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reinstall Android on Oneplus6 or Oneplus6t Device After Installing Mobile Linux</title>
      <link>https://kosmosghost.github.io/posts/reinstall-android-on-oneplus6-or-oneplus6t-device-after-installing-mobile-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 19:50:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kosmosghost.github.io/posts/reinstall-android-on-oneplus6-or-oneplus6t-device-after-installing-mobile-linux/</guid>
      <description>Did you install a Mobile Linux Operating System onto your Oneplus6 or Oneplus6t device, and you want to go back to android? Well, you&amp;rsquo;re in luck as it&amp;rsquo;s a pretty straight forward process.
First, download the package from Oneplus. This can be done by going to service.oneplus.com/us. Scroll down to the image that says Software Update and then click on it. You will now be at a page that has a list of devices with links for firmware for the devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing PostmarketOS With Full Disk Encryption on Oneplus6 Oneplus6t Devices</title>
      <link>https://kosmosghost.github.io/posts/installing-postmarketos-with-full-disk-encryption-on-oneplus6-oneplus6t-devices/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 19:30:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kosmosghost.github.io/posts/installing-postmarketos-with-full-disk-encryption-on-oneplus6-oneplus6t-devices/</guid>
      <description>Installing PostmarketOS on the Oneplus 6/6t devices is pretty easy, and you will have a linux operating system on your phone with full disk encryption. By following this short tutorial you can have a mobile linux operating system on your phone in no time, but this tutorial assumes you are using linux for doing the install. Before you start you are going to need a few tools:
Android tools for fastboot - On Fedora: sudo dnf install android-tools</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
